<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bitotsav</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="contact_us_sponsors_about_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="events_fragment">Events Fragment</string>
    <string name="home_fragment">Home Fragment</string>
    <string name="brought_to_you_by">Brought to you by Amazon</string>
    <string name="bitotsav_theme">Play | Pause | Reload</string>
    <string name="register_fragment">Register Fragment</string>
    <string name="timeline_fragment">Timeline Fragment</string>
    <string name="informal_fragment">Informal Fragment</string>
    <string name="flagship_fragment">Flagship Fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_timeline">TimelineActivity</string>
    <string name="flagship">Flagships</string>
    <string name="t_shirt">Book T-Shirt</string>
    <string name="support">Support Us</string>
    <string name="t_shirt_fragment">T-Shirt Fragment</string>



    <string name="sample_desc">THis is just a sample descriptionTHis is just a sample description
        THis is just a sample descriptionTHis is just a sample description
        THis is just a sample descriptionTHis is just a sample description
        THis is just a sample descriptionTHis is just a sample description
        THis is just a sample descriptionTHis is just a sample description
        THis is just a sample descriptionTHis is just a sample description
        THis is just a sample descriptionTHis is just a sample description
        THis is just a sample descriptionTHis is just a sample description
        THis is just a sample descriptionTHis is just a sample description
        THis is just a sample description</string>

    <string name="instructions">
Hello gamer!!
\n\nThe different packages for registration are as follows:
\n1. OVERALL PACKAGE- Rs.900
\n(includes access to all the day events and the nights+bitotsav t-shirt+wrist band+goodies)
\n\n2.PER DAY REGISTRATION
\n\nDAY 1(HINDI BAND NIGHT-JHANKAAR)- Rs.300
\n(includes access to all the day events of that particular day and the hindi band night+wrist band)
\n\nDAY 2(ENGLISH BAND NIGHT-ELLYSIUM)- Rs.350
\n(includes access to all the day events of that particular day and the english band night+wrist band)
\n\nDAY 3(EDM)- Rs.400
\n(includes access to all the day events of that particular day and the EDM night+wrist band)
\n\nDAY 4(PRO NITE)- Rs.450
\n(includes access to all the day events of that particular day and the pro night+wrist band)
\n\nNOTE:
\n1. For accomodation, one needs to pay Rs.200 extra in which Rs. 100 is security money which will be refunded back once you vacate the room.
\n2. T-shirt can be purchased after a payment of Rs.200 from the registration desk in case one has not taken the overall package.
\n3. If a team/individual wishes to participate only in a particular event, they need to register themselves for that particular day for which the event is scheduled.
\n4. Payment once done will be non-refundable in any circumstances.
    </string>

    <string name="notif_body">The venue has been changed from shor bagh to IC Arena. Please inform everybody as soon as possible. Enjoy!!The venue has been changed from shor bagh to IC Arena. Please inform everybody as soon as possible. Enjoy!!</string>

    <string name="sample_desc_small">THis is just a sample descriptionTHis is just a sample description
        THis is just a sample description</string>
    <string name="todo_dassam">The Dassam Falls is situated at 34 km from the city of Ranchi on Ranchi-Tata road near the Taimara village. The place is also known as Dassam Garh. The major water source of this waterfall is River Kanchi, which falls here from an altitude of 144 feet. The unique feature of this fall is that when the waterfall is seen, 10 water streams are also seen falling.\n</string>
    <string name="todo_jonah">One has to descend 722 steps to admire the surroundings. Water in the falls drops from a height of 43 meters (141 ft). There is a tourist rest house which encloses a Buddhist shrine with a deity of Lord Gautama Buddha. A temple and an ashram dedicated to Buddha were built atop Gautama Pahar by the sons of Raja Baldevdas Birla. A fair is organized in Jonha every Tuesday and Saturday</string>
    <string name="todo_hundru">The Hundru Falls is created on the course of the Subarnarekha River, where it falls from a height of 98 meters (322 ft) creating one of the highest water falls in the state.  At the base of the Hundru Falls, there is a pool, which serves as a bathing place.</string>
    <string name="todo_rock_gardens">A beautiful garden set amidst The Ranchi Lake. This garden is an ideal place for relaxing especially after dawn when the temperature cools down. The lake of the Kanke Dam is located close to the Rock Garden of Ranchi. The place is visited by many people who are attracted to this garden by the endless horizon and the gentle touch of the nature, which can be found here. The Rock Garden is also used as a picnic spot, where large groups of people can spend quality time together</string>
    <string name="todo_ranchi_lake">Located at the base of the majestic Ranchi hill, this lake was constructed in the` year 1842 by a British National Colonel Onsely. It is centrally located and has boating facilities. Being well-maintained by the authorities, this is the perfect spot to enjoy a relaxed evening and is ideal for picnics. The Ranchi hill itself is a popular tourist destination, it also has a Shiva Mandir at its top and one can get a panoramic view of the entire city from there.</string>
    <string name="todo_birsa_zoo">The Jaivik Udyan in Jharkhand is often termed a zoological garden, because of the wide range of animal life that it showcases and it is worth a visit. The wildlife sanctuary of Jaivik Udyan in Jharkhand is especially popular not only in the state but all over the country of India, because of its quite unique collection of a variety of species of mammals.  The Jaivik Udyan in Jharkhand is often termed a zoological garden, because of the wide range of animal life that it showcases and it is worth a visit.</string>
    <string name="todo_tagore_hill"> The first thing you will notice is the graffiti sprayed on huge boulders, followed by a white archway. Once you climb the hill you can see the house where Tagores elder brother stayed. It has been recently renovated by Tagore buffs. The view of the city from the hill top is remarkable. This place is the perfect getaway if you are looking for a peaceful place away from the city noises. There is a Ramakrishna Ashram at the foot of Tagore hill. It is advisable not to venture out here after dark.</string>
    <string name="todo_panch_ghat"> In its bid to find its way through the hard and jagged terrain, the Banai River branches itself out in five different streams, generating ubiquitous singing rivulets through the cluster of rock In spite of the presence of a large number of high waterfalls in the area, the Panchghagh Falls are a tourists preference for being viewed as the safest of all. The water falls from a lesser height, making it safe for tourists to enjoy in the rapid flow of water. Most of the people arrive here for picnic with family and friends. According to plans of the Tourism Department of the Government of Jharkhand, the Panchghagh Waterfalls will soon get a kiosk, a restaurant, toilets, fast-food joints, lighting facilities and a watchtower</string>
    <string name="todo_kanke_dam"> Offsetting the huge, dark boulders of the Gonda hills lies the huge reservoir of the Kanke Dam. This lake is great for fishing and makes a perfect picnic spot.You may climb down the steps leading to the water and take a walk around the lake. Youll find numerous water hyacinths floating on the lakes rim. And if you are feeling slightly famished, there are a number of food vendors around to satisfy your hunger pangs.</string>
    <string name="todo_birsa_deer">Birsa Deer Park is situated on the Ranchi-Khoonti road near Hatia, at 11 km south-west of Ranchi. This park is a fast constructed one, surrounded by hundreds of species of deer. It started with a total of 15 dears, which grew with the growing number of visitors. Its main attraction is the Park safari that provides a clear view of the roaming deers throughout the park.</string>
    <string name="todo_patratu_valley">Flanked by hills covered with lush green trees, red and violet flowers and honey bees humming, the Pithouria-Patratu Valley is no less attractive than the valleys on the Gangtok-Nathula, Dehradun-Mussouri and Raxaul-Kathmandu roads in terms of natural elegance. Of course, the hills along the Pithouria-Patratu stretch are devoid of snow, unlike the ones on Gangtok-Nathula. But green saal, sakhuwa and bamboos with flowers, in a riot of colours, more than make up for the absence of snow. The jingle-jangle of waterfalls and rivulets rushing through the stones, sooth the ears, and eyes, even more than any maestros music.</string>
    <string name="todo_kaveri">It is a casual restaurant serving pan Indian dishes, buffets and thalis. Kaveri is one of the most famous veg restaurants in ranchi and also one of the oldest.
Address: Shop 9-11, 1st Floor, G.E.L. Church Shopping Complex,Main Road, Mahatma Gandhi Marg, Ranchi, Jharkhand 834001
Phone:088888 88888</string>
    <string name="todo_kathi">Kathi Kabab is a Indian Restaurant located in Main Road in Ranchi. It serves Indian and fast food and is famous for its tandoori chicken, kebabs and chicken chilli. It also has great options for the vegetarians.
Address: Main road, Ranchi, 834001
Phone: 0651 2101 218
    </string>
    <string name="todo_snacks_valley">It is a fast food center located near Sujata Chowk, Main Road. It is famous for its rolls. It is well known among the young crowd.
Adress: PP Compound, Main Road, Sujata Chowk, Ranchi
Phone:  9835502406 </string>
    <string name="todo_subway">It is the famous American fast food chain that serves amazing build-your-own sandwiches and salads. The menu has variety of options both for the vegetarians as well as the non-vegetarians.
Address: Shop No.50232, Hi Street Mall, Opp Church Complex, Main Rd, Ranchi, Jharkhand 834001
Phone: 0651 233 1744</string>
    <string name="todo_nirvana">Nirvana - Vegetarian Fine Dine is one of the popular Restaurant located in Parivar Heights, Sarjana Chowk, Main Road ,Ranchi. It is famous for presenting the dishes in an innovative and unique manner giving them a twist.
Address: Upper Bazar, Ranchi, Jharkhand 834001
Phone: 098351 12711</string>
    <string name="todo_royal_retreat">The Royal Retreat is a luxury hotel situated out of the hustle and bustle of the city, Ranchi. The hotel houses a restaurant, serving flavorsome delicacies that will surely pamper the appetite. It also features well-equipped conferencing and banqueting venues, making it a perfect base for business as well as leisure travellers.
Address: Krishna Nagar, Booti, Ranchi, Jharkhand 835217
Phone: 081029 18108</string>
    <string name="todo_bnr">Chanakya at Ranchi is a unique business class and tourist oriented hotel. It is practically on a walk –in configuration for passengers arriving by rail and is also easily accessed from the airport. The property is spread over 5 acres in the heart of the town and is strategically located near the Govt. departments and the top corporate and industrial houses.
Address: Station Rd, Ranchi, Jharkhand 834001
Phone: 0651 246 1211</string>
    <string name="todo_radisson">Ideally situated for both business and leisure travel to the "City of Waterfalls", the Radisson Blu Hotel Ranchi invites guests to experience truly outstanding service and modern amenities in the heart of Jharkhands vibrant capital. Active guests appreciate premium services like an on-site spa, a swimming pool and the OXYGEN fitness center, and our grand meeting space for 600 allows corporate travelers and bridal parties to impress guests with minimal commutes
Address: Main Road Kadru Diversion, Opp Chamber of Commerce, Ranchi, 834001
Phone: 0651 660 2222</string>
    <string name="todo_dominos">Dominos offers a wide range of mouthwatering veg pizzas like, double cheese margherita, country special, peppy paneer, deluxe veggie etc and lip smacking non-veg pizzas like barbeque chicken, chicken Mexicana, and the very popular non-veg supreme with your choice of crust and toppings
Address : PLOT NO. 1793 / A, OPPOSITE OF RANCHI CLUB, RANCHI MAIN ROAD RANCHI, JHARKHAND
Phone: 0651 - 2332641-48 </string>
    <string name="todo_kfc">Fast-food chain known for its buckets of fried chicken, plus wings and sides.
Address: Shop # 10,11,12, Siromtoli Chowk, Old, Hazaribag Rd, Gungutoli, Kanka, Ranchi, Jharkhand 834001
Phone: 086538 48265 </string>
    <string name="todo_madhuban">It is one of the oldest dhabas which has now transformed into a well-known hotel. Youngsters find it a very economical hangout spot.
Address: 33, N.H. Road, Bangaon, Ormanjhi, Ranchi, Jharkhand 835219
Phone: 0651 257 6496 </string>
    <string name="todo_urban_brava">Class Elegance Grandeur Redefined .The First in its kind in Ranchi. Recover just not discover.Come Spoil yourself...Just not follow...Create yourself.Address: Hindpiri, Ranchi, Jharkhand 834001
Phone: 88778 87778 </string>
    <string name="todo_capitol_hill">Capitol Hill is 2.7 km from Ranchi Lake and 5.9 km from Birsa Munda Airport. It offers internet facility, restaurant and bar. Located minutes away from Hatia Railway Station and Khadgarha Bus Station in Ranchi, Capitol Hill is a popular 4 star property.
Address: Mahatma Gandhi Marg and Main Road, Ranchi, Jharkhand 834001
        Phone: 0651 233 1331 </string>
    <string name="todo_bunk">Bunk’N’Bonk is Jharkhand’s first Urban Sports Center that Non-stop mixes gaming, partying and dining into an exhilarating experience. Bunk’N’Bonk is a sports-centric entertainment venue offering a perfect blend of entertainment, innovative games, interactive sports, socializing, eating and relaxation areas. </string>
    <string name="todo_ameoba">Amoeba is in the heart of the city and is an ideal place to spend a few hours. The bowling alleys are well maintained and they even have railings in the gutter to give those amateurs to get a score to be proud of the variety at the arcade parlor is quite impressive - multi-player car racing conduits, air hockey, basketball games. It is a nice to place to hang out with your buddies. You will really enjoy bowling here. They have ample space to accommodate around 50 people in bowling area itself. </string>
    <string name="todo_spring">There is a Gaming zone and a pool parlor in one of the biggest malls Ranchi, spring city mall. It is in the heart of the city and is an ideal place to spend a few hours and a great place to hang out. The gaming zone is a favorite among the youngsters. </string>
    <string name="todo_fun">It is a very well equipped video game parlour located in Galaxia mall, Ratu Road. It is one of the most happening places in Ranchi. One should really go there to enjoy with their friends. </string>
    <string name="todo_ranchi">Discover Ranchi</string>
    <string name="todo_howtoreach">How to reach</string>
    <string name="how_to_reach">Reaching ranchi</string>
    <string name="nigths">Nights</string>

</resources>
